卡马里
Kamali!
斯科特
Scott!
醒醒
Come on!
快醒醒
快醒醒  快
Come on. Come on.
快醒醒
Come on.
卡马里哪去了
Where is Kamali?
去他妈的戈麦斯
Fuck Gomez!
哥伦比亚  波哥大
你知道那个混蛋
You know that asshole
又回到船舱帮忙救你出来吗
came back to the boat to help me get you out?
要不是他  你早就死了
If he hadn't have, you wouldn't be here.
"那个混蛋"是指卡马里?
"That asshole" being Kamali?
没错
Yeah.
除了他还有谁会干这种蠢事
Who fuckin' does that?
他不是刚发现你是摩萨德特工嘛
He just found you're a Mossad agent.
如果换作我
If it were me...
你不会救我的
You would have let me die.
没错
Yeah.
是啊
我也不会
Me, too.
你看
You see?
所以说我们是天生一对
That's why we're made for each other.
我得走了
I have to go.
妈的  不是吧
Fuck. Really?
瑞贝卡
Rebecca.
他们还有多久能到
How long till they get here?
谁
Who?
你一直在等的摩萨德小队
That Mossad team that you're waiting for.
别想蒙我
Don't bullshit me.
我知道卡马里还在这镇上
I know that Kamali's still in this town.
否则你也不会跟我待在这
Otherwise you wouldn't be here with me.
说不定我是真的想跟你在一起
Maybe I want to be here with you.
切
Yeah.
这是摩萨德的行动
Well, this is a Mossad mission.
是你打乱了我的计划  还记得吗
You crashed my party, remember?
没错
Yeah.
他们什么时候到
When do they get here?
24小时内
24 hours.
该死
Shit.
没错
Yeah.
那肯定来不及
It'll be too late.
那时他早就跑了
He really will have gone by then.
除非咱们俩合作
Unless, of course, you and me team up,
一起去抓他
together,
找到他的机会可以翻倍
and double our chances of getting him.
他每到一个城市做生意
He's got a safe deposit box
都会去银行租个保险箱
in a bank in every city he operates in.
在里面存放情报信息  现金
Dead-drops for intel, cash,
护照  还有安全屋的列表
passports, and a list of safe houses.
他会去其中的一个安全屋
He will be in one of those houses,
等待戈麦斯帮他越境
waiting for Gomez to get him across the border.
只要找到那个保险箱  我们就能抓到卡马里
We get the safe deposit box, we get Kamali.
很好
Nice.
你高兴什么
What are you so happy about?
因为...
Because...
我们要去抢银行了
we're going to rob a bank.
我们要去抢什么?
We're going to do what?
那里算不上银行
It's not really a bank.
保险箱位于中央证券交易所
The safety deposit boxes are under the Central Stock Exchange.
你耍我  你不说是家银行吗
You kidding me? You told me it was a bank.
那也有金库  你还是可以扮劫匪的
It has a vault. You still get to play bank robber.
棒极了  这就够了
Awesome. That's all I needed.
你干嘛?
What?
小时候没玩过警察抓小偷吗
You didn't play cops and robbers when you were a kid?
玩过
Yeah.
让我猜猜
Then let me guess.
你都是扮警察的对吧  迈克尔
You played the cop, didn't you, Michael?
但你现在得做小偷了  到底干不干
Well, now you got to play the robber. So you in or out?
如果这么做能瞒过洛克
If this is what keeps us from telling Locke
不让他知道我们弄丢了卡马里  那我就干
that we've lost Kamali, then I'm in.
很好  我们要去抢银行了
Bingo. Right! We're robbin' a bank.
这是你的地盘  你说怎么抢
It's your town. How do you want to do it?
你们已经见过米格尔·戈麦斯了
Well, you know Miguel Gomez already.
没错  他喜欢猫
Yeah, loves cats
还很擅长用火箭筒
and he's great with an RPG.
这是他弟弟  拉乌
And this is his brother, Raoul.
他没有继承戈麦斯家族的优良基因
He didn't win the Gomez family genetic lottery.
不仅吸毒而且有心脏病  不过
Cocaine addict with a heart condition, but still,
多亏了他哥哥
thanks to big brother,
他当上了中央证券交易所的主席
president of the Central Stock Exchange.
拿枪顶着那肥佬  他就会带我们通过安检
Stick a gun in his fat gut and he'll walk us through security.
这就是你的计划?  大摇大摆的走进去?
That's your plan? To walk in?
难道我们有时间挖地道吗
Do we have time to dig a tunnel?
今天是周日
It's Sunday.
人少好办事
Minimal bodies on the ground. Keeps it simple.
拉乌身边有什么安保措施吗
Does Raoul have any protection?
两个保镖  一个司机
Two bodyguards and a driver.
人手倒是少得很
That's light.
因为所有人都知道他哥哥是谁
That's 'cause everybody knows who his brother is.
他每周日都会去
Sundays he always walks
西蒙玻利瓦尔公园遛他那条破狗
his ugly-ass dog in the Simon Bolivar Park.
我们假设一下
Let's just say, for the sake of argument,
如果中间出了岔子
that something does actually go wrong
招来了警察
and the real police come running.
我是不会对恪尽职守的警察开枪的
I'm not shooting some cop just for doing their job.
这里可是哥伦比亚
This is Colombia.
出了事没人会先想着找警察
The police are never the first people you call.
没错  地球人都知道应该找"茅山道长"
No. Everyone knows it's the Ghostbusters.
瞧你这逼样
You're twat.
你们废话真多
You guys talk too much.
行了  别闹了
Enough. Please.
马丁内斯
Martinez?
谢谢  如果出了岔子
Thank you. If something goes wrong,
会有一支佣兵部队赶到现场
there'll be a private military response team heading your way.
他们也归贩毒集团所有
Just another cartel-owned company.
这群人在警察接到报警之前就能赶到
Now, these boys bust through before the cops even hear about it.
他们绝对惹不起
You don't want to fuck with them.
没错  只要照计划进行就惹不到他们
Yeah, well, we won't have to if it goes according to plan.
因为一切都会照计划进行
'Cause it will go according to plan.
抢银行嘛  能出什么岔子  对吧
It's a bank robbery. They never go wrong, do they?
黎巴嫩  贝鲁特
别着急
You took your time.
我忙着呢  快走
I've been busy. Keep walking.
你是比较绝望
You're faintly desperate,
但我觉得你不会杀我
but I don't think you're going to shoot me.
再跑就打断你的腿
Put a bullet through your leg if you try to run again.
过奖了  我哪跑得过你啊
I'm flattered you think I could outrun you.
听说那些法国人在找你
I heard the French were looking for you.
我们已经达成了协议
We came to an agreement.
你呢  在12号分部吗
What about you? Section 12?
20号
20.
他们的装备最差了  你找我干什么
The bluntest of their instruments. What do you want with me?
我在追杀我凶手的
Found your name in a book
雇主名单里发现了你的名字
of matches on a man who was trying to kill me.
恐怕在贝鲁特想要取我性命的杀手
I imagine there's more than one hired killer
远不止一个
in Beirut with my name in his pocket.
你有没有出卖我
Did you give me up?
我出卖的人已经够多了
I have enough blood on my conscience.
出卖你的人绝不是我
Whoever betrayed you, it wasn't me.
-你好  -你好
- Hola. - Hola.
最好别动  死胖子
I wouldn't, fat man,
除非你想在内脏上打补丁
unless you got a puncture repair kit ready.
你们知道我是谁吗
You have any idea who I am?
底细早就摸清楚了
Oh, we know exactly who you are.
救命
Help!
起来  咱们散散步  快点
Come on. Let's take a walk. Come on.
乖乖  身手不错
Damn! You're good.
熟能生巧嘛
Practice.
对不住咯
Excuse me.
我一直在跟踪李奥·卡马里
I've been tracking Leo Kamali.
他是地产开发商
Leo Kamali's a property developer.
卡马里是"印钞机"  没有他洗的脏钱
Kamali is a money man; without the cash he launders,
朱海瑞和他的手下不过是一群
Al-zuhari and his followers would be nothing but
成天在西方大使馆门前示威的
a bunch of angry Arabs
愤怒的阿拉伯刁民
burning flags outside western embassies.
抱歉  帮不了你  金盆洗手了
Sorry, I can't help you. I'm out of the game.
放屁
Bullshit.
你人绝对不是来这度假的
You're here, you're in it, selling
只要有人肯出价
whatever information you can dig up
你就会把挖到的情报卖出去
to just about anyone who'll pay for it.
我令你反感吗
Do I disgust you?
就因为我不够忠诚  名誉败坏?
Is it my lack of loyalty or honor?
现在有哪个国家或政府能做到这点
Name one government or nation that has any.
难道我是这世上唯一出卖情报的人?
Am I supposed to do it on my own?
世界是被你们搅混的...
You have built this world...
你和你的同类
you and your kind.
我明白了
Oh, I see.
看来你的顾虑还不少
I suppose that means you have scruples.
为了得到想要的真相  你愿意做些什么
And what would you do to get to the truth you're looking for, eh?
打断我这个老头的腿吗
Shoot an old man in the leg?
瑞秋  你知道我在你身上看到了什么吗
You know what I see when I look at you, Rachel?
我看到一个迷失的姑娘
I see a girl who is lost,
站在悬崖边缘  这你应该相信我
on the edge, and you should trust me on this
因为这一幕我早见识过了
because I've seen it all before.
派你来这的人
The same people who sent
就是十年前派出莱瑟比的那位
you out here sent Leatherby out 10 years ago--
你知道莱瑟比?
You know Leatherby?
知道别人是怎么说他的吗?
What do they say about him?
知道别人又是如何解释这位将才突然
How do they explain how a soldier of his caliber
背叛祖国转而为敌军效力这件事的吗?
suddenly switches sides and works for the enemy?
如果你仍然执迷不悟
If you carry on along this path,
这也会发生在你身上
it'll happen to you.
我只想要你告诉我
All I want you to tell me
来杀我的人是不是朱海瑞派来的
is whether or not it was Al-zuhari who sent his men to kill me.
你这问题有毛病
That's the wrong question--
是吗  那应该是什么
Well, why don't you tell me what the right one is?
过去三个月里  六名特工被杀
Six intelligence officers have been killed in the last 3 months.
汽车炸弹  绑架  暗杀数之不尽
Car bombings, kidnappings, assassinations.
这是一次有条不紊的大清洗
This is a systematic cleansing of the closet.
朱海瑞把苗头指向
Al-zuhari is targeting
那些会对他构成威胁的人
people specifically who are dangerous to him.
就像你这样的
People like you.
911事件发生前  基地组织也干过这事
It's what Al-Qaeda did before 9/11.
看来要出大事了
So something's coming.
什么事
What?
几周前  我听到风声
A couple of weeks ago, I heard a whisper
说有人在搜集有关西方国家军事基地的情报
about a man looking for intel on western military bases.
什么情报  哪些基地
What intel? Which bases?
所有情报  应有尽有
All of them, everything:
物资  人员  火炮和时间表
materiel, personnel, artillery, schedules.
我问过自己  我说"塞巴斯汀..."
You know, I asked myself, I said, "Sebastian...
"真正有价值的不是情报本身"
"The real value here is not the intel,
"而是搞清楚到底谁要这些情报"
it's knowing who really wants this information."
所以我自称卖家
So I put myself up as a seller.
让别人以为我能搞到他们想要的情报
I let it be known that I had what they wanted.
后来呢
So what happened?
后来
What happened?
朱海瑞的手下当街拦住我
Al-zuhari's men snatched me off the street,
把我塞进后备箱  三小时后
bundled me into the trunk of a car, and drove me for 3 hours
把我带到他们位于贝卡谷地的一个训练营
into the Bekaa Valley to one of their training camps.
你见到朱海瑞本人了?  他在这?
You met Al-zuhari? He's here?
没人见过他  见过的都死了
Nobody meets him, not anymore.
他们限我三周内交出情报
His people gave me 3 weeks to deliver.
但你是不会这么做的
But you won't.
是做不到
I can't.
我没有他们要的情报...
I don't have what they want...
但现在你至少知道朱海瑞的目标
But now you know that Al-zuhari
是西方国家的军事基地
is targeting western military bases.
他们会杀了你的
They'll kill you.
但是
Well,
我有自己的做事原则
but I've always played by my own rules.
你可以逃跑
You could run.
往哪儿逃
Where to?
在这儿我至少可以痛快地下几盘西洋双陆棋
Least I can get a decent game of backgammon here.
跟我走
Come in with me.
帮我们找到朱海瑞的基地
Help us find Al-zuhari's base.
你真是勇气可嘉  不是吗
You're a brave thing, aren't you?
我有个女儿...
I had a daughter--
妈的
Shit!
该死  糟糕
Oh, fuck! Shit!
有没有觉得在一个地方待久了自会厄运连连?
Ever get that feeling you outstayed your welcome?
死人开不了口了
Well, he's giving us nothing.
油门总是踩得比较重
Always was a little heavy on the gas.
上车
Get in.
飞机已经待命
There's a plane standing by.
我们去哥伦比亚
We're off to Colombia.
格瑞死了
Gray is dead.
他知道朱海瑞想要...
He knew that Al-zuhari was up to--
喘口气吧  少校
Take a breath, Major.
上了飞机再说
Debrief in the air.
不用客气
Don't mention it.
我总想抢劫一家银行
I've always wanted to rob a bank.
那不是银行  斯科特  是家交易所
It's not a bank, Scott, it's an exchange.
下车  死胖子
Out, fat man.
说了这里没钱
I told you there's no money here.
没关系  我们不要你的钱
Yeah, we don't want your money.
不要钱要什么
No? Then what?
好了  你们需要让他
OK, you need to get him
输入他的安全码才能进去
to punch in his security code on the way in.
地下室那个需要语音识别
When you get down to the vault, it's voice recognition.
输入密码  让我们进去
You put in the code, we're gonna go in.
敢乱叫就杀了你
Any fuss, we'll kill you.
好好输密码  死胖子
Put the fucking number, Humpty Dumpty.
-你觉得打他有用吗  -或许没有
- You think that helps?  - Probably not.
但是这让我觉得很爽
It makes me feel good.
好了  管用吧
Here you go. See? And it works.
总部  我们进去了
Zero, we're in.
地下室就在你们前方那部扶梯下面
OK, the vault's down the escalator ahead of you,
前台有一名警卫
and there's one guard at the desk.
戈麦斯先生病了
快来帮忙
我们搭右边那部扶梯
We're gonna take that escalator to your right.
继续走  死胖子
Keep moving, fat man.
你怎么慢下来了
What are you slowing down for?
好了  语音识别  说话
All right, voice recognition. Speak.
不
No.
拿来
Come on.
别耍我  死胖子
Don't fuck with me, fat man.
说话
Speak.
拉乌·戈麦斯
Raoul Gomez.
来人了
Heads up.
或许我可以为你们服务一下
Perhaps I can be of some service to you.
不用了  谢谢
我们没事  警官
你会说西班牙语
一点点啦
Ah, poquito.
二位长得很漂亮
没错  她确实很漂亮
这真是一座浪漫的城市
你不觉得吗
这里不准停车  快走
There's no parking here. Move away.
对不起  警官
Sorry, officer.
哪个是卡马里的
Which one's Kamali's?
我不知道
对不起  我不知道
卡马里的
Kamali's.
卡马里是谁啊
我知道你认识他
I know you know him.
原来是你
Ah, it's you.
你这吃里扒外的臭婊子
You treacherous fucking whore!
哪个是卡马里的
Which one's Kamali's?
-哪个  -我不认识他
- Which one?  - You don't know him!
如果我背叛了李奥·卡马里
If I betray Leo Kamali,
那连我弟弟都保护不了我了
not even my brother could protect me.
你也不了解我  十秒之后
And you don't know me, so in 10 seconds,
我就用你的脑浆子重新打点这个地下室
I'm gonna redecorate this vault with 50 shades of gray matter.
十  九  八
10...9...8...
七  六  迈克
7...6--Mike!
好的  交给我了
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
抢劫啦
快来人啊
对不住了  老兄
Sorry, mate.
总部  我们暴露了
Zero, we've been made.
警卫拉响了警报  我们还有多长时间
A guard raised the alarm. How long have we got?
警报常规反应时间为四分钟
Response time normally 4 minutes.
见鬼
Shit.
咱们继续  是哪个
All right, where was it?
-六  五  -求求你了
- 6...5...  - Please.
四
4...
三
3...
二
2...
一  到底是哪个
1. Which one was it? Huh?!
见鬼
Fuck!
到底发生了什么
What the fuck's happening?
你害他心脏病发作了
You've given him a heart attack!
-我又不是故意的  -好极了
- I didn't fuckin' mean it! - Yeah!
我不是故意的
I didn't mean it!
我知道你有什么借口  他看起来没心脏病是吧
Oh, i know, it's not like he's a likely candidate, is he?
-去死吧你  -总部  死胖子出事了
- Fuck you, Scott! - Zero, we've got a little problem with the big guy.
拉乌怎么了
Well, what the fuck happened to Raoul?
他失去意识了
All right, he's unconscious.
总部  你能黑入交易所的数据库吗
Zero, can you hack into the exchange's database?
我无法赶在他们到达之前完成
I can't hack in before they come.
他是我们与卡马里的唯一联系
He's the only link we have to Kamali.
-那你们最好把他弄醒  -快点弄醒
- Well, then you better wake him up. - Fast.
-你得把他弄醒  -我?
- You're gonna have to revive him.  - Me?
-凭什么  -因为你害他心脏病发作
- Why?  - Because you gave him the heart attack!
那又如何  我又不是故意的
Yeah, well, I didn't mean to.
她是我救的  轮到你了
I did her. It's your turn.
她可不是体重两百磅
Her, not a 200-pound
吸毒加口臭的大猩猩  达米恩
coke-snorting gorilla with halitosis, Damien.
为了女王和国家  迈克尔
Queen and country, Michael.
-全看你觉悟  -操
- That's all I'm saying.  - Fuck!
你们的大麻烦来了
You've got a bigger problem than that--
敌军已进入范围
X-rays inbound.
天呐  我来吧
Ohh! I'll do it.
上帝  真恶心
Oh, my God, that's disgusting.
我正在尝试启动攻击程序
I'm trying to initiate hack protocols.
搜索"卡马里"无果
OK, I've got nothing under "Kamali."
给我名字  我给你们数字
Give me a name, I'll give you a number.
他母亲叫什么
What's his mother's name?
莉萨·库伯
Lisa Cooper.
父亲叫约瑟夫·卡马里
Father--Youssef Kamali.
都不对  不是莉萨
Negative--no Lisa,
不是库伯  也不是约瑟夫
no Cooper, no Youssef.
快点  醒醒
Come on! Wake up!
还剩两分钟
Two minutes.
等等  艾丝特
Wait. Esther.
试试艾丝特
Try Esther.
-他喜欢这个名字  -你开什么玩笑
- He likes the name.  - You kidding me?
你们已经聊起婴儿名字了?
You guys already talk baby names?
也不对
Negative.
那一定是这个
It has to be.
是什么
What does it mean?
思达
Star.
没错  约翰·查尔斯·思达  553号
Yep, got it. John Charles Star. 553.
553  553
553, 553.
-在那  -没错  就是它
Right there. Yep, there it is.
开工  老兄
Let's go, buddy.
注意  武装佣兵正向你方移动
Be advised, armed APC's arriving your location.
快啊  迈克
Come on, Mike.
他死了
He's gone.
你开什么玩笑
You kidding me?
麻烦得一个个解决  快啊  迈克尔
One problem at a time. Come on, Michael.
马上离开
Get out now.
这绝对不会出岔子是吧  斯科特
Fuckin' never goes wrong, does it, Scott?!
-抢银行真他妈爽是吧  -去你妈的
- Robbing banks is fucking great! - For fuck's sake!
给我闭嘴
Shut up!
-操  -喂
- Fuck! - Hey!
我操
Fuck it!
你们看呐
Now, look at that!
好极了
Nice.
他妈的
Bloody hell.
你以后要是再被开除军籍
You know, if this soldiering thing doesn't work out,
说不定能去当个医生
maybe you could be a doctor.
-我考虑考虑  -有什么发现吗
- Thinking about it. - Anything?
是啊  还真说不准
Yeah, possibly.
总部  我们马上撤退
Zero, we're coming out right now.
收到  从前门撤退
Roger. Front of the building.
好了  撤  准备好了吗  撤
All right, go, go. Ready? Moving.
再见了  死胖子
See ya, fat man.
总部  我看到你们了
Zero, I've got visual on you.
注意  敌方已就位
Be aware. X-rays in position.
该死  迈克  前方地势空旷  敌军众多
Fuck! Mike, we got a lot of open ground, a lot of numbers.
用烟雾弹
Let's smoke it up.
在这
In there.
烟雾弹来了
Fuckin' smoke.
瑞贝卡  一旦向前冲就不能停
Rebecca, once we go, we got to keep moving.
听到了没
You copy that?
好
Yes.
达米恩  冲
Hey, Damien, move it.
-前进  -趴下
- Move! - Stay down!
趴下  趴下
Stay down! Stay down!
他妈的
Goddamn it!
迈克
Mike!
-迈克  -嗯
- Mike! - Yeah!
你还好吗  中枪了没有  没事吧
You all right? Did you get hit? You OK?
没事  只是咬到舌头了  前进
Yeah, I just bit my fucking tongue! Now move!
走了  前进  上
Movin'! Movin'! I'm movin'!
趴下  都他妈趴下
Down! Stay the fuck down!
趴下  该死的
Stay down! Shit!
准备前进  迈克尔
Get ready to move, Michael!
阿迈
Mikey!
上
Go!
冲
瑞贝卡  上
Rebecca, move!
不
No!
操
Fuck!
不  不
No, no.
不
No!
不要  不要
No, no, no, no.
不
No.
走啊
Move!
水  水
Water. Water. Water.
来了  挺住
Here. Come on.
-来吧  没事吧  -不  不
- Come on. All right? - No, no.
-喝水吗  -不  不
Water? No, no, no. No.
你不用这么做
You don't need to do that.
以色列啊  你且听
主乃吾之上帝
主乃命中注定
我在你面前...
向你叩谢...
-达米恩  -在
- Damien? - Yeah.
-我在这  -我看不见了
- I'm here. - I can't see.
我们得走了
We got to move!
-我知道  -快
- I know! - Come on!
斯科特  我们得走了
Scott, we got to move.
如果你想带上她就带上
If you want to bring her, we'll bring her.
她死了  迈克
She's gone, Mike.
她死了  给
She's gone. Here.
拿着这个  找找有用的东西
You take this and you find something useful!
-走  -丢下他们不管吗
- Go! - We're leaving them?
这或许能带我们找到卡马里
If this gets us Kamali,
这才是当务之急
that's all that counts.
操你妈
Fuck you!
我们撤
Let's move!
给我下车  快滚开
Get the fuck out of the car! Get the fuck out of here!
出去  快滚  快
Get out! Get out of here! Move!
去死吧
Die!
我们跟上
总部  敌人跟上来了
Zero, we've got X-rays incoming.
-操  开什么玩笑  -谢谢
- Fuck! You kidding me? - Thank you!
去你的
Fuck you!
又来?  向左  向左
Not again! Move, move, move.
去他妈的  迈克尔  开的漂亮
Fuck it out, Michael. Nice driving.
一旦卡马里得知金库遭窃
Once Kamali knows the vault's been hit,
他就知道我们离他不远了
he'll know we're closing in.
是吗  给我一点时间
Yeah? Just give me a second.
我们最好能找到卡马里在哪
We better find out where Kamali is.
找到了
Got it.
安全屋
Safe houses.
总部  这里是B组
Zero, this is Bravo Team.
总部  这里是B组  你们找到了什么
Zero, this is Bravo Team. What have you got?
我们找到了三处贩毒集团使用的安全屋
I've got coordinates for 3 safe houses used by the cartel.
收到
Roger that.
是哪一个
Which one?
戈麦斯喜欢用工地做掩饰
You know, Gomez uses construction as a front.
他们把钱投进房地产
They put money into housing developments.
有处安全屋在工地里  肯定就是那了
One safe house is a construction site. That must be it.
正在发送坐标
Sending the coordinates through now.
收到
Roger that.
B组  我们要回天帐了
Bravo Team, we're heading back to the Crib.
你没事吧  伙计
You with me, mate?
没事
Yeah.
-检查我漏掉的情报  -是  长官
- Check this for anything I've missed. - Yes, ma'am.
汇报情况
Sit-rep?
B组已到达安全屋
Bravo Team has arrived at Safe House.
没有进一步行动
No further activity.
上
Go.
-他在里面吗  -总部  我们要进去了
- Is he inside? - Zero, moving in.
确认地面位置
Confirm situation on the ground.
B组注意  敌军正在向你方靠近
Bravo, be advised. X-rays heading in your direction.
看来卡马里真在这
Least we know Kamali's here.
上去  哥们
Go ahead, bud.
来了
Coming up.
瑞贝卡呢
Where's Rebecca?
你的好兄弟戈麦斯把她打死了
Your buddy Gomez shot her.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
斯科特  外面来人了
Scott, outside.
有多少
How many?
唉  多极了
Uh, too many.
你总是一惊一乍的
There's always too many.
好吧  这次是真的  该死
Yeah, well, this time, there really is. Shit.
手放背后
Hands behind your back.
听到我说话吗
Do you hear me?
把卡马里放出来
Send Kamali out!
说不定我会放你们一条生路
Maybe I'll let you live!
给你们一支烟的时间
You have until I smoke this.
放我走  留在这里你们都得死
Let me go. Stay here, you die.
-和瑞贝卡一样死得不明不白  -给我闭嘴
- Like Rebecca, for nothing. - Shut the fuck up!
我向上帝发誓  要死也是你先死
I swear to God, you're gonna die first!
斯科特  帮我把窗户堵上
Scott, help me cover these windows.
来了
Coming in.
该死
Fuck.
就这么简单  总部
There, simple. Zero.
我们已找到目标  但我们被包围了
We have the asset secure, but we're surrounded.
妈的
Fuck it.
我早就猜到自己会死于枪林弹雨
I always knew I'd go out like this.
-是吗  -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
-你呢  -没想过
- You? - No.
我觉得我会活到最后
No, I actually thought I'd make it.
领领退休金什么的
Pick up my pension, all that.
-任时光荏苒什么的?  -没错  等我老了
- Get old and shit? - Yeah, get old,
将我的事迹编成睡前故事讲给孙子辈听
bedtime stories for the grandkids,
在入土前让他们知道我以前有多英勇
tell them how great I was before my knees went.
那你这牛可就吹大了  迈克尔
Well, then you'd be lying to them, Michael.
没错  就知道你会这么说
Yeah, well, there is that.
-你呢  -没想过
- What about you? - No.
我从来没这么想过
I never saw it like that for me.
总部  我们该怎么处理人质
Zero, what do you want me to do with the asset?
杀掉人质
Terminate the asset.
说再见吧
Make your peace.
-就现在  -你不能杀我
- Now. - You can't shoot me!
我当然可以
Yeah, I can.
-你不能  -为什么
- No, you can't. - Why is that?
因为我是中情局特工
Because I'm CIA.
-你放屁  -杀了他
- Bullshit. - Shoot him.
-开始祷告吧  -他们冲进来了
- Start saying your prayers. - They're coming.
我是个中情局卧底
I'm a CIA undercover agent.
我的代码是"天马"
My codename is Pegasus.
我的上级是奥古斯特·凡·伯格
My controller is August Van Berg.
十五年前  他们从哈佛商学院招我入中情局
I was recruited out of Harvard Business School 15 years ago.
我一直以卧底身份打入朱海瑞的网络
I'm under deep cover to get inside Al-Zuhari's network.
-该死  -打电话给兰利
- Shit. - Call Langley
你们不是有联络人吗
you have contacts there.
打电话给他们  问问"天马"的事
Call them, ask about Pegasus!
总部  你听到了吗
Zero, you gettin' that?
我们正在联系兰利
We're trying to get a line to Langley now,
但是需要点时间
but we need more time.
我要查一位卧底  "天马"
I'm looking for a handle--Pegasus.
我们没时间了  到底要不要杀他
We haven't got time. Do I shoot him or not?
他是恐怖分子  快杀了他
He's a fucking terrorist. Go, shoot him, yes.
没错  因为有兰利的支持
Yes, I am, and with Langley behind me,
我才能一路走到现在的位置
I went right to the fucking top.
我现在已深入敌后  如果你杀了我
I'm inside now, and if you shoot me,
你就失去了阻止朱海瑞的唯一希望
you lose the only hope anyone has of stopping Al-Zuhari.
没人比我更接近朱海瑞
No one is closer than me.
没有其他人能够发现真相
No one else got a fucking chance of finding out the truth.
他正在密谋一项行动
And he is planning something.
-重大行动  -他在密谋什么
- Something massive. - What's he planning?
-我还不知道  -真是个好借口
- I don't know yet. - How convenient.
但我已接近真相  我需要时间
But I am close. I need more time.
这不正是我们的共同目的吗  阻止恐怖分子
That's what we're all here for, right? To stop the terror?
同志们  我已见识你们的能耐
You guys, I have seen what you can do,
令我印象深刻
and it's impressive,
但我可以用我的方式完成更多
but I can do more my way.
你们必须相信我
You just have to trust me.
你们都很清楚  门一旦打开你们就死定了
When that door opens, you are dead. You know it.
但我可以带你们离开这里
But I can get you out of this.
我是你们今天活着出去的唯一的希望
I am the only hope you have of living out this day!
给我松绑  把你们的武器给我
Untie me and give me your weapons.
-去他妈的  -总部  他说的是真是假
- Oh, fuck off! - Zero, is he talkin' shit or not?
我不知道  我还在联系有关人员
I don't know. I'm trying to get through to the right people.
斯科特  杀了他  他杀了巴克斯特
Scott, shoot him. He killed Baxter.
他们对他严刑拷打
They were torturing him.
我还能怎么做
What else could I do?
闪开
是嘛  那瑞贝卡呢  她怎么说
Yeah? And Rebecca? Huh?!
我也希望她还活着
I wish she hadn't died,
但她和我们一样  时刻冒着生命危险
but she took the same risks that we all do.
如果我在撒谎  你们得死
If I'm lying, you die.
如果我说的是实话
If I'm telling the truth,
你们还是得死
you still die...
躲得过今天  躲不了永远
Just not today!
我是中情局特工  你们得相信我
I am CIA. You have to trust me.
没有  没有"天马"这个人
Negative, negative. There is no Pegasus.
B组  经证实  他不是中情局特工
Bravo, be advised. He is not CIA.
重复  他不是中情局特工
I repeat, he is not CIA.
你个狗日的骗...
You lying mother--
我真怀念朝九晚五做警察那时的正直
I miss the honesty of day-to-day police work.
你没事吧
Oy. You OK?
还好
Yeah.
好吧  听起来也没比我好到哪去
Yeah, you sound like I feel.
好吧
Yeah.
-我梦到咱们骑车穿越墨西哥了  -是吗
- I dreamed we were riding bikes through Mexico. - Ha!
我尝到了玛格丽特的滋味
I can taste margaritas.
伙计  那是你嘴里的血腥味
That's just the blood in your mouth, mate.
妈的
Aw, shit.
一种特殊的南美货
A uniquely South American device,
根据电牛棒改装
based upon the cattle prod,
但是专门为了...
but manufactured specifically for...
拷打人类而设计
The torture of human beings.
没错  拉乌
Exactamente, Raoul.
你感觉如何啊  拉乌
How you doing, Raoul?
你不该在医院里接受缩胸手术吗
Shouldn't you be in the hospital gettin' a breast reduction,
你个死胖子
you fat bitch?
怀念这个吗
And miss this?
高压  低频
High voltage--heh!-- but low current.
你以为这样我们就会开口吗
And you think that's gonna make us talk?
你不知道我们接受过拷打训练吗
You don't think we've trained for this?
不是这么玩的  他负责说
No, no, no, no. He talks.
你只管叫就可以了
You scream.
轮到你了
And now you.
-抬头  -滚开
- Huh? - Fuck off.
只要开口  你朋友就不必受刑了
You talk, and your friend doesn't suffer.
你们来这的目的是什么  说
Now what are your intentions towards me and my people, hmm?
对不住了  阿迈
Sorry, Mikey.
嗯  动手吧  斯科特
Yeah, do it. Do it, Scott.
我对你满满都是爱哟  兄弟
I got nothin' but love, man.
我知道你们是英国情报局的
Look, I know you're British Intelligence.
你们来哥伦比亚做什么
Why are you in Colombia?
你看  你全搞错了伙计
See, that's where you're wrong, buddy.
我不是英国人
I'm not British,
他也和聪明不沾边
and he's certainly not intelligent.
双关:他不是情报人员
说的对  说的好极...
Oh, yes, yeah. Great, that's fun--
你可是个毒贩子啊
You're a fuckin' drug dealer.
倒是掐指算算呐  蠢货
Connect the dots, retard.
好吧  你说
OK. Your turn.
等等
No, no, no.
用这档  来
For this one. Heh!
看来你和我哥之间
Ha! I see things between you and my brother
有一点个人恩怨
have gotten a little personal.
你这是要干嘛
What'd you do that for?!
你应该先问他问题的
You got to ask him a question first!
因为这让我觉得很爽
Because it makes me feel good.
你们杀了维克多·乌尔诺夫  为什么
Look, you killed Viktor Ulyanov. Why?
谁
Who?
操  你别摸我啊
Fuck, don't touch me.
阿卡帝·乌尔诺夫的儿子
The son of Arkady Ulyanov--
我的客人
my guest in my fucking house!
我不知道你在说什么屁话
I have no idea who you're talking about.
迈克
Mike.
干嘛
Yeah?
我允许你回答一个问题  迈克尔
You can answer a question now, Michael.
你这么快就没种了  老兄
Are you wussing out on me now, mate, huh?
他们交待了些什么
What did they tell you?
什么都没说
Nothing.
没我们想象得好玩对吧  拉乌
This is not as much fun as we'd hoped, hey, Raoul?
不如把他们的手砍下来算了
Let's just cut their fucking hands off.
不
No.
我有办法撬开他们的嘴
I'll make them talk...
用这个
with this.
不不不  别剪那个
No, no, no, no, no, not that one.
别傻了
Don't be foolish.
他们很有价值
They're valuable.
交给我来看管
Let me have them.
他们弄伤了我哥哥  还杀了维克多
Look, they hurt my brother. They killed Viktor.
要向阿卡帝交待的人是我  不是你
I'm the one that has to answer to Arkady, not you.
如果你怕他多过朱海瑞
If you fear him more than you fear Al-Zuhari,
那你就错了
you're making a mistake.
这里是我的祖国  李奥  错了也是我自作自受
This is my country, Leo. It's my mistake to make.
没错
Yes, it is.
你到底站在哪一边啊  伙计
Whose fuckin' side are you on, man, huh?!
给我  你这个死胖子
Give me that, you fat fuck!
迈克
Mike!
喂  米格尔
Hey, Miguel.
谢谢
Thanks.
不用客气
You're welcome.
你们快走吧
Get out of here.
什么  你还留在这儿
What, you're staying?
我的身份没暴露  唯一的目击者也死了
My cover's still good. The only witnesses are dead.
你要不要跟我们回去一趟
How about you come back with us
解释下为什么中情局里
and you explain why nobody at the CIA
没有人听说过你
has ever fucking heard of you?!
这主意棒极了  迈克尔
That is a great idea, Michael.
多谢夸奖
Yeah, thanks.
对不住了  死胖子
Sorry, fat man.
2010年
2010...
美国在多哈的军事基地遭到神经毒气攻击
A nerve gas attack on an American military base in Doha.
14名军人死亡
14 servicemen dead.
朱海瑞声称对此负责
Al-Zuhari claimed credit.
没错
Yeah.
你早就知道
You knew?
但你却束手旁观
And yet you did nothing.
你不好奇为什么只死了14个人吗
Why do you think only 14 people died?
你可以告诉我为什么...
Do you care to tell me why it is exactly
中情局没有你的档案?
that Langley has no record of you?
你的机密等级有多高
How high does your clearance go?
足够高
High enough.
显然还不够
Apparently not.
道尔顿少校  住手吧
Major Dalton, that's enough.
怎么回事
What's going on?
这家伙是谁
Who the hell is this?
我是谁?
Who am I?
我是中情局反恐中心副局长
I'm the Deputy Director of the CIA Counterterrorist Center,
奥古斯特·凡·伯格
August Van Berg!
这个人  你殴打的这个人
And this man, this man you've been beating
他是个英雄  是位卧底特工
is a hero! He's an undercover agent!
那为什么中情局没有他的档案
Why the hell does Langley have no records of him, then?
所有可否认的秘密行动都没有记录
There are no records of deniable deep cover operations!
这你应该知道
You should know that!
中情局让一个卧底资助
What does the CIA think of an inside man
你们极力打击的恐怖组织是唱的哪一出啊
who's helping fund the very terrorism they're trying to put a stop to?
我不需要向你解释我们的行动  少校
I don't have to justify our actions to you, Major.
那你他妈来这做什么
What the fuck are you doing here?!
我现在要做什么
What am I doing now?
现在我要想办法把李奥送回去
Now I'm trying to figure out how to get Leo back into the loop
还不能让他暴露身份
without him being fucking compromised!
他不能回去
He's not going back.
我必须回去
Oh, yes, I am!
朱海瑞要是发现你抓到了我  他就跑了
Al-Zuhari finds out you've taken me, he's gone!
他会人间蒸发  三年内都别想找着他
He's disappeared! He's in a cave for the next 3 years!
等等
Hang on.
我不是在跟你协商
These are not negotiations.
我是在告诉你接下来该怎么做
This is me telling you how it is gonna go down!
给你看个东西
Let me show you something.
天呐  李奥
Christ, Leo.
所以  这就是接下来该做的事
So, this is how it's "Gonna go down."
卧底归我  情报共享
We run your asset, we'll share the intel,
不然就判他个25年终身监禁
or he gets 25 years to life.
这做不了证据
You can't use this.
那我们走着瞧
You try me.
你会毁了我们十多年的心血
You'll destroy a decade of work.
我不想毁掉任何东西  我只想加以利用
I don't want to destroy anything. I want to use it.
就算交易吧
Call it a trade.
你...  你以为我是吃软饭的?
You--you think I can't make a call?
我会让我的老板通知白厅
I'll get my bosses to talk to Whitehall.
你和你的白痴手下
You and your band of merry men
都会被发配到福克兰群岛放哨
will be pulling sentry duty in the fucking Falklands!
起码知道了我们会与企鹅作伴
At least you know we'll stand with the penguin.
我们不能信任他
We can't trust him.
你得服从命令  少校
You will do as ordered, Major.
好吧
Ok.
我知道你们不信任我
I understand that you don't trust me.
这不奇怪
Why should you?
但如果你们决定要信任我  那你们必须明白
And, if you decide to, then you should know
我不能向你们做任何保证
I cannot guarantee you anything.
朱海瑞肩负使命  信仰坚定
Al-Zuhari has a mission and he has faith,
他为了达成目标  可以不惜一切代价
and he will sacrifice anyone and everything to achieve his goals:
你  我  任何人
you, me, anyone.
你们也必须做好同样的心理准备
You must be prepared to do the same.
你们已经感受到了我们每天经受的痛苦
You have tasted what we must live with every day.
除非你们的政府从所有
Until your governments withdraw from all lands
不欢迎你们的土地上撤军
where you are unwanted,
我们将携手世界上所有受压迫国家的兄弟们
we and our brothers from oppressed nations of this earth
让安拉的怒火撒在你们的头上
will rain the fire of Allah on your heads.